Finding Aid of the Dave Berkman Papers, 1958-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1958-2016, UWM Manuscript Collection 347; 4.2 cubic ft. (5 boxes, including 38 audio cassettes) 1 videocassette 448 digital audio files (22 GB)
  - 2. Radio Broadcasts, 1991-2009
    - B. Guest Hosting Appearances, 1997-2007
      - Mother Jones Political Poll, 16 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:31) (Electronic 220)
        With Michael Scherer, D.C. correspondent for Mother Jones
      - International Medical Ethics and Military Doctors, 16 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:09) (Electronic 221)
        With M. Gregg Bloche, professor of law & health policy, Georgetown University
      - Could US be Tried for War Crimes?, 18 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:52:09) (Electronic 222)
      - How Media Affects Agricultural Policy, 18 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:13) (Electronic 223)
        With Mark Kastel, Director, Organic Integrity Project
      - Single Women's Votes, 21 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:52:36) (Electronic 224)
        With Christina Desser, co-director, Women's Voices, Women Vote
      - Labor Market Needs Immigration Reform, 21 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:46:09) (Electronic 225)
        With Jim Staudenraus, field director, Federation for Immigration Reform
      - Labor Unions are Failing Workers, 21 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:45:01) (Electronic 226)
        With Linda Chavez, Author of "Betrayal"
      - Who Was Best President in 20th Century, 22 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:02) (Electronic 227)
      - Fair Trade Chocolate, 22 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:48:06) (Electronic 228)
        With Valerie Orth, organizer for Global Exchange
      - Prison Abuse in Wisconsin, 24 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:52:38) (Electronic 229)
        With Doug Hissom, senior political writer, Shepherd Express
      - Government is Overregulating US, 24 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:54) (Electronic 230)
        With Wayne Crews, adjunct scholar, CATO Institute
      - Bullying in the Workplace, 24 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:18) (Electronic 231)
        With Dr. Gary Namie, president, Workplace Bullying & Trauma Institute
      - Green Party Convention, 25 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:25) (Electronic 232)
        With Jo Chamberlain, co-chair, National Green Party
      - Controversy Re: 'Fahrenheit 9/11', 25 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:45:00) (Electronic 233)
        With Robert Thompson, Syracuse University, director, Center for Study of Popular TV
      - Is Public Radio Really Public?, 25 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:42:45) (Electronic 234)
        With Steve Rendell, senior analyst, FAIR
      - Media Are Having an Integrity Crisis, 08 July 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:17) (Electronic 235)
        With Bonnie M. Anderson, author, "News Flash: Journalism, Infotainment & the Bottom-Line Business of Broadcast News"
      - The Movie 'The Corporation', 08 July 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:54) (Electronic 236)
        With Mark Achbar, producer & co-director, "The Corporation"
      - Republican Critics of Bush, 08 July 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:57) (Electronic 237)
        With Kevin Phillips, author, "American Dynasty"
      - Study of American Patriotism, 09 July 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:02) (Electronic 238)
        With Karlyn Bowman, resident fellow, American Enterprise Institute
      - Campaign Ads Influence, 09 July 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:40) (Electronic 239)
        With Ken Goldstein, assistant professor, UW-Madison; director, Advertising Project
      - Conflict Resolution Strategies, 06 August 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:52:43) (Electronic 240)
        With Bonnie Block, non-violence trainer
      - Granny D & Trippi, 06 August 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:58) (Electronic 241)
        With Granny D/Joe Trippi, US Senate candidate for New Hampshire
      - Wisconsin Prisons, 27 August 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:50:50) (Electronic 242)
        With Adrian Lomax, prisoner activist, writer
      - Lawsuit Abuse - Fact or Rhetoric?, 27 August 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:45:43) (Electronic 243)
        With Stephanie Mencimer, Washington Monthly contributing editor
      - Banjo as a Political Instrument, 24 September 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:06) (Electronic 244)
        With Michael Miles, banjo performer
      - Macho Culture Disrespects Anything Foreign, 24 September 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:26) (Electronic 245)
        With William Murphy, professor, Anthropology & African Studies, NYU
      - Shooting Prone Iraqi Media Controversy, 19 November 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:03) (Electronic 246)
        With Bob Zelnick, Chairman, Journalism department, Boston University
      - Sly's Aunt Jeminah Controversy, 19 November 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:54) (Electronic 247)
        With John Sylvester, AM host, program director, of WTDY
      - Ending the Drug War, 26 November 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:46) (Electronic 248)
        With Ethan Nadelmann, executive director, Drug Policy Alliance
      - Gay Strategies for Anti-Gay Rights Battles, 26 November 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:29) (Electronic 249)
        With Michael Cole, communications director, Human Rights Campaign
      - Democrats Must Be Progressive, 24 December 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:50:48) (Electronic 250)
        With Donnie Fowler, Wesley Clark's campaign manager
      - Ukraine Presidential Election, 24 December 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:27) (Electronic 251)
        With Charles Wise, director, Ukrainian Parliamentary Development Project
      - Mad Magazine, 31 December 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:29) (Electronic 252)
        With John Ficarra, editor, Mad Magazine
      - Republican Control of the House, 14 January 2005, 2 digital audio files (0:40:53 and 0:50:55) (Electronic 253-254)
        With Craig Gilbert, D.C. bureau chief, Milwaukee Journal Sentinel
      - The Rather Forged Document Report, 14 January 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:41:13) (Electronic 255)
        With Tim Graham, director of media analysis, Media Research Center
      - School for Raucous Pundits, 16 February 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:51:10) (Electronic 256)
        With Joshua Green,senior editor, The Atlantic
      - Computers' Negative Effects in Schools, 16 February 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:50:55) (Electronic 257)
        With Todd Oppenheimer, author, "The Flickering Mind"
      - Workers of the World Unite?, 04 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:51:04) (Electronic 258)
        With David Moberg, senior editor, In These Times
      - Black Contract w/ America on Moral Values, 04 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:42:38) (Electronic 259)
        With Bishop Harry Jackson, author, "High-Impact African-American Churches"
      - Peace Proposals for Palestine, 23 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:51:06) (Electronic 260)
        With Teddy Katz, Israeli peace activist
      - Election Impact of Schiavo Case, 23 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:43:30) (Electronic 261)
        With Paul Gronke, professor, Reed College
      - Coalition against Patriot Act, 23 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:05) (Electronic 262)
        With Peyton Knight, executive director of American Policy Center
      - Free Parking Effects, 24 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:50:45) (Electronic 263)
        With Donald Shoup, professor of Urban Planning, UCLA
      - Legal Aspects of Schiavo Case, 24 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:43:31) (Electronic 264)
        With Donald Downs, Law professor, UW-Madison
      - Retire Rich, 24 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:03) (Electronic 265)
        With David Bach, founder of FinishRich, Inc
      - Gas Prices & Driving, 25 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:51:04) (Electronic 266)
      - Housing Sex Offenders, 25 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:30) (Electronic 267)
        With Stan Stojkovic, dean of Social Welfare, UWM
      - Your Words for Graduates, 27 May 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:50:44) (Electronic 268)
        With Dick Haven, Communications professor, UW-Whitewater
      - America's Nuclear Waste, 27 May 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:43:43) (Electronic 269)
        With Bob Halstead, nuclear waste consultant
      - Public Broadcasting Funding, 13 July 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:47:55) (Electronic 270)
        With Dave Berkman, columnist, Shepherd Express
      - Time U.S. Had Viable Energy Policy, 25 November 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:52:27) (Electronic 271)
        With Tyson Slokum, director, Energy Research Program
      - Latest Developments in Iraq, 25 November 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:43:11) (Electronic 272)
        With Ed Turzanski, senior fellow at Foreign Policy Research Institute
      - Your Views on the News, 07 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:35) (Electronic 273)
      - Freedom Now Milwaukee, 07 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:42:19) (Electronic 274)
        With Matt Nelson, Freedom Now organizer
      - Sports Journalism Today, 07 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:01) (Electronic 275)
        With Bob Wolfley, sports columnist, Milwaukee Journal-Sentinel
      - Gas Prices, 12 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:43:27) (Electronic 276)
        With Erin Roth, executive director, Wisconsin Petroleum Council
      - Media DIS-honors Awards, 12 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:00) (Electronic 277)
      - Military Strike Against Iran, 12 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:44:07) (Electronic 278)
        With Dale Herspring, Political Science professor, Kansas State University
      - Myths of Technology Change, 14 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:39:43) (Electronic 279)
        With Bob Seidensticker, author, "Future Hype"
      - Your Views on the News, 14 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:02) (Electronic 280)
      - Don Imus Firing, 13 April 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:30:17) (Electronic 281)
        With Dave Berkman & Paul Krassner, media critic & political commentator
    - C. Other Appearances, 1991-2009
      - How the Media Has Dealt with Milwaukee Serial Murder Case, 30 July 1991, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 28)
      - Clarence Thomas Sex Harassment Hearings, 14 October 1991, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 29)
      - With Michael Weinzierl, 2 March 1992, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 30-31)
      - Rape Coverage Forum, 31 March 1992, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 32)
      - Jesse Anderson Case, 27 April 1992, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 33)
      - Press Coverage of Jesse Anderson Case, 28 April 1992, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 34)
      - Media Coverage of the Barbara Anderson Murder, 5 May 1992, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 35)
      - Telecommunications Reform Bill, 1 February 1996, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 36)
      - AFL-CIO State Chapter, 7 March 1996, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 36)
      - Media Performance in Year Since Terrorist Attack, 11 September 2002, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 37)
      - New Television Season, 20 September 2002, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 37)
      - Media Reversal on Weapons of Mass Destruction, 14 July 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:49:33) (Electronic 282)
      - Media Coverage of the Great Blackout of 2003, 14 August 2003, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 38)
      - Dominance of Scandal and Celebrity Fluff Over Hard News, 15 August 2003, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 38)
      - New York Blackout Coverage, 01 August 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:50:39) (Electronic 283)
      - The Sinclair Broadcast, 25 October 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:41:42) (Electronic 284)
      - Media Coverage of Pope's Death, 08 April 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:46:48) (Electronic 285)
      - Newsweek Controversy, 19 May 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:40:31) (Electronic 286)
      - Media Coverage of Michael Jackson Trial, 14 June 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:20:58) (Electronic 287)
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting Funding & Independence, 23 June 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:08) (Electronic 288)
      - The Shield Law/Judith Miller, 07 July 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:22:58) (Electronic 289)
      - Pabst City/Robert's Nomination, 15 August 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:53:54) (Electronic 290)
      - Katrina Media Coverage, 15 September 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:59) (Electronic 291)
      - Eric Vonn Show, 17 November 2005, 1 digital audio file (1:03:07) (Electronic 292)
      - Eric Vonn Show, 29 November 2005, 1 digital audio file (1:30:29) (Electronic 293)
      - Eric Vonn Show, 29 November 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:14:38) (Electronic 294)
      - Mining Disaster Reporting, 04 January 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:11:28) (Electronic 295)
      - Eric Vonn Show, 05 January 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:02:28) (Electronic 296)
      - Weekly Panel, 09 January 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:11:10) (Electronic 297)
      - Media Coverage of 2006 Elections, 14 January 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:42:32) (Electronic 298)
      - Readers Choose Newspaper Story, 30 January 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:19:26) (Electronic 299)
      - Weekly Panel, 07 February 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:09:11) (Electronic 300)
      - Weekly Discussion, 14 February 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:12:55) (Electronic 301)
      - Weekly Panel, 15 February 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:53:15) (Electronic 302)
      - Sunday Talk Shows' Conservative Tilt, 20 February 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:34:30) (Electronic 303)
      - TV Without Commercials, 28 March 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:43:30) (Electronic 304)
      - Media in the Black Community, 26 June 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:42:15) (Electronic 305)
      - Media Independence, 04 July 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:11) (Electronic 306)
      - This Week's Local News, 06 July 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:05:09) (Electronic 307)
      - Panel on Local News, 13 July 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:58:34) (Electronic 308)
      - Bush says "Shit"/Indecency Fines, 19 July 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:40:36) (Electronic 309)
      - Media Scooter Libby Trial, 20 July 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:48:52) (Electronic 310)
      - This Week's Panel Discussion, 20 July 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:48:20) (Electronic 311)
      - Panel Discussion of Local News, 27 July 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:08:51) (Electronic 312)
      - International News Panel, 03 August 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:54:37) (Electronic 313)
      - Backstory Panel Discussion, 10 August 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:01:20) (Electronic 314)
      - Thursday's Panel Discussion, 24 August 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:00:02) (Electronic 315)
      - Media Confessed Benet Killer, 28 August 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:40:45) (Electronic 316)
      - Local Candidates Election, 07 September 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:41:39) (Electronic 317)
      - State & Local Election Media Coverage, 12 September 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:45:19) (Electronic 318)
      - Local Politics, 28 September 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:58:11) (Electronic 319)
      - Fox News 10th Anniversary, 04 October 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:41:27) (Electronic 320)
      - 6 Coming Elections, 12 October 2006, 3 digital audio files (0:14:00, 0:20:49, 0:21:53) (Electronic 321-323)
      - Air America's Failure, 20 October 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:31) (Electronic 324)
      - Week in Review Panel, 02 November 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:03:27) (Electronic 325)
      - Weekly Panel, 16 November 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:02:18) (Electronic 326)
      - Weekly Discussion, 21 December 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:57:51) (Electronic 327)
      - Weekly Panel, 04 January 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:55:33) (Electronic 328)
      - Weekly Panel, 11 January 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:03:16) (Electronic 329)
      - Weekly Panel, 18 January 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:04:40) (Electronic 330)
      - Weekly Panel, 20 January 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:07:34) (Electronic 331)
      - Weekly Panel, 24 January 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:57:39) (Electronic 332)
      - Weekly Panel, 01 February 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:06:23) (Electronic 333)
      - Weekly Discussion, 22 February 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:03:11) (Electronic 334)
      - Weekly Panel, 08 March 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:04:16) (Electronic 335)
      - Proposed Cable Legislation, 22 March 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:45:11) (Electronic 336)
      - Don Imus Firing, 16 April 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:40:57) (Electronic 337)
      - Weekly Panel, 19 April 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:56:39) (Electronic 338)
      - Weekly Panel, 26 April 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:50:07) (Electronic 339)
      - Weekly Panel, 10 May 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:02:49) (Electronic 340)
      - Weekly Discussion, 20 May 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:01:58) (Electronic 341)
      - Weekly Panel, 24 May 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:51:25) (Electronic 342)
      - Weekly Panel, 31 May 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:43:47) (Electronic 343)
      - Weekly Panel, 07 June 2007, 2 digital audio files (0:18:28 and 0:49:34) (Electronic 344-345)
      - Weekly Panel, 14 June 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:01:38) (Electronic 346)
      - BBC's Liberal Bias, 20 June 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:47:06) (Electronic 347)
      - Weekly Panel, 21 June 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:05:44) (Electronic 348)
      - Weekly Panel, 28 June 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:02:15) (Electronic 349)
      - Weekly Panel, 05 July 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:01:08) (Electronic 350)
      - Weekly Discussion, 12 July 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:59:17) (Electronic 351)
      - Weekly Panel, 19 July 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:53:27) (Electronic 352)
      - Weekly Panel, 02 August 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:34:29) (Electronic 353)
      - Weekly Discussion, 09 August 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:39:00) (Electronic 354)
      - Weekly Panel, 16 August 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:33:11) (Electronic 355)
      - Weekly Panel, 30 August 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:41:14) (Electronic 356)
      - Laborfest Live, 03 September 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:33:05) (Electronic 357)
      - Weekly Panel, 13 September 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:38:14) (Electronic 358)
      - Weekly Panel, 20 September 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:31:28) (Electronic 359)
      - Recent Media Issues in the News, 21 September 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:40:43) (Electronic 360)
      - Weekly Panel, 27 September 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:32:00) (Electronic 361)
      - Weekly Panel, 04 October 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:30:35) (Electronic 362)
      - Weekly Panel, 11 October 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:38:18) (Electronic 363)
      - Weekly Panel, 18 October 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:46:29) (Electronic 364)
      - Weekly Panel, 25 October 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:01:11) (Electronic 365)
      - Weekly Panel, 01 November 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:28:16) (Electronic 366)
      - Weekly Panel, 08 November 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:09:02) (Electronic 367)
      - Weekly Panel, 08 November 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:36:07) (Electronic 368)
      - MSNBC Liberal Lineup, 09 November 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:40:51) (Electronic 369)
      - Weekly Panel, 15 November 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:52:57) (Electronic 370)
      - The Man Show, 23 November 2007, 1 digital audio file (2:10:40) (Electronic 371)
      - Weekly Discussion, 29 November 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:05:13) (Electronic 372)
      - Weekly Panel, 06 December 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:57:04) (Electronic 373)
      - Weekly Panel, 13 December 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:49:40) (Electronic 374)
      - Weekly Panel, 20 December 2007, 1 digital audio file (1:07:26) (Electronic 375)
      - Weekly Panel, 27 December 2007, 1 digital audio file (0:50:38) (Electronic 376)
      - Weekly Discussion, 10 January 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:52:38) (Electronic 377)
      - Weekly Panel, 17 January 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:39:03) (Electronic 378)
      - Weekly Panel, 24 January 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:47:04) (Electronic 379)
      - Coverage of the Presidential Race, 01 February 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:40:43) (Electronic 380)
      - Weekly Panel, 07 February 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:54:22) (Electronic 381)
      - Weekly Panel, 14 February 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:30:15) (Electronic 382)
      - 21/2008, 21 February 2008, 1 digital audio file (2:24:39) (Electronic 383)
      - Weekly Panel, 28 February 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:49:19) (Electronic 384)
      - WMCS 3rd Anniversary Show, 29 February 2008, 1 digital audio file (2:28:39) (Electronic 385)
      - Weekly Panel, 06 March 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:48:30) (Electronic 386)
      - Weekly Panel, 20 March 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:47:24) (Electronic 387)
      - Press Coverage of Obama's Bad Week, 24 March 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:42:54) (Electronic 388)
      - Hours on WMCS, 27 March 2008, 1 digital audio file (2:33:08) (Electronic 389)
      - Monday on Eric Vonn, 31 March 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:52:05) (Electronic 390)
      - Weekly Panel, 03 April 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:54:37) (Electronic 391)
      - Weekly Panel, 10 April 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:47:18) (Electronic 392)
      - Weekly Panel, 24 April 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:47:42) (Electronic 393)
      - Weekly Panel, 01 May 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:11:08) (Electronic 394)
      - Weekly Panel, 08 May 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:50:19) (Electronic 395)
      - Dave Solo On Weekly Panel, 08 May 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:19:28) (Electronic 396)
      - Weekly Panel, 15 May 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:17:12) (Electronic 397)
      - Weekly Panel, 29 May 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:22:25) (Electronic 398)
      - Weekly Panel, 05 June 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:27:08) (Electronic 399)
      - Where Do You Get Your Campaign News?, 20 June 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:40:47) (Electronic 400)
      - Comments on George Carlin, 25 June 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:00:43) (Electronic 401)
      - Weekly Panel, 08 September 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:34:16) (Electronic 402)
      - Weekly Panel, 11 September 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:47:38) (Electronic 403)
      - Weekly Panel, 18 September 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:45:30) (Electronic 404)
      - Weekly Panel, 25 September 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:43:32) (Electronic 405)
      - Weekly Panel, 02 October 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:43:18) (Electronic 406)
      - Weekly Panel, 09 October 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:46:53) (Electronic 407)
      - Weekly Panel, 16 October 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:51:46) (Electronic 408)
      - Weekly Panel, 23 October 2006, 1 digital audio file (1:44:31) (Electronic 409)
      - Weekly Panel, 30 October 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:53:45) (Electronic 410)
      - Weekly Panel, 06 November 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:47:49) (Electronic 411)
      - Willy's WORT Show, 10 November 2008, 1 digital audio file (0:54:41) (Electronic 412)
      - Weekly Panel, 20 November 2008, 1 digital audio file (1:47:46) (Electronic 413)
      - Media Coverage of Palin, 13 January 2009, 1 digital audio file (0:40:54) (Electronic 414)
      - Chimpanzee Cartoon & Free Speech, 26 February 2009, 1 digital audio file (0:43:49) (Electronic 415)
      - Party Splintering Coverage, 07 October 2009, 1 digital audio file (0:49:17) (Electronic 416)
      - The White House & Fox News, 27 October 2009, 1 digital audio file (0:38:52) (Electronic 417)
      - Issues in Media News, 27 November 2009, 1 digital audio file (0:44:28) (Electronic 418)